远在罗马、巴比伦和埃及文明之前，坎达克文明就存在了
Before Rome, before Babylon, before the pyramids, there was Kahndaq.
坎达克，公元前2600年
KAHNDAQ, 2600 BC
作为地球上最早的自治民族
The first self-governing people on Earth,
坎达克一直是权力和文明发源地
Kahndaq was a center of power and enlightenment.
几世纪以来， 繁荣昌盛
For centuries, they thrived.
但后来…
But then...
阿克顿王来了
came King Ahk-Ton.
阿克顿王利用军权篡夺了政权，进而变成了暴君
Using the army to seize power, Ahk-Ton became a tyrant.
但他还有更黑暗的野心
But he had even darker ambitions.
阿克顿痴迷于黑魔法
Obsessed with dark magic,
他的终极目的是锻造萨巴克之冠
Ahk-Ton's real goal was to forge the Crown of Sabbac.
将远古世界六魔的力量灌注入皇冠
If infused with the powers of the six demons of the ancient world,
这样就能让阿克顿王获得战无不胜的力量
it would make Ahk-Ton invincible.
为了制作皇冠，他需要永恒金属
To make the crown, he needed Eternium.
那是一种只在坎达克存在的稀有魔法金属
A rare mineral of magic properties, found only in Kahndaq.
所以阿克顿王奴役他的子民
So he enslaved his own people...
强迫他们挖掘
and forced them to dig.
永恒金属
Eternium.
坎达克文明正摇摇欲坠
Kahndaq was teetering on the brink.
他们需要……
What they needed...
放开他
Get off him.
...一位英雄
...was a hero.
我们为什么要内哄?
Why are we fighting each other?
记住我们真正的敌人是谁
Remember who our real enemy is.
跟我来
Come with me.
看，是永恒金属
Look. Eternium.
让我看看
Let me see that.
国王感谢你
The king thanks you.
他应该奖励他
He's supposed to reward him.
你觉得应该吗?
Is that right?
我只想要我应得的
I want what I'm owed.
你想要奖赏?
You want a reward?
国王感谢你的效力
The king thanks you for your service.
你也想要国王的奖赏?
You want the king's reward too?
不，我儿子接受国王的仁慈
No, but my son accepts the king's mercy.
我不可能一直保护你
I won't always be here to protect you.
我不需要保护
I don't need protection.
我想要自由
I want to be free.
如果我们所有人一起战斗，我们可以推翻国王
If we fight together, we could overthrow the king.
让别人当英雄吧……
Let someone else be the hero...
那些人最后都会进坟墓
the graveyards are full of them.
别做梦了，回去工作吧
Stop dreaming and go back to work.
人民需要有人能承载他们的希望
Someone to hold the hopes of the people.
即使希望渺茫
Even when all hope seems lost.
如果我们有更多的英雄……
If we had more heroes...
那我们的自由就不是梦了
then maybe our freedom wouldn't be a dream.
自由
Freedom.
阿克顿王深知星星之火可有燎原之势
King Ahk-Ton knew that this spark could quickley ignite a fire.
于是他下令灭了星星
And so he ordered that it be snuffed out.
人们以为这个男孩是殉葬者
They thought they were getting a martyr.
然而……
Instead...
他们却目睹了奇迹
they got a miracle.
巫师委员会，地球的魔法守护者……
The Council of Wizards, the magical guardians of the earth...
你被选中了
You have been chosen.
...试图恢复平衡
...sought to restore the balance.
他们赋予他上古诸神的力量
They empowered him with the gifts of the ancient gods.
把男孩变成了…
And turned a boy...
成为捍卫者
into a champion.
沙 赞
S-H-A-Z-A-M.
快点
Hurry.
把它给我
Give it to me.
但是皇冠已经完成了
But the crown had already been completed.
把它给我
Give it to me.
当捍卫者来到宫殿向他挑战时……
And when the Champion arrived at the palace to challange him...
阿克顿王国王召唤了它的恶魔力量
King Ahk-Ton summoned its demonic power.
在随后的战斗中，宫殿被毁
In the ensuing battle, the palace was destroyed,
但捍卫者胜利了
but the Champion was victorious.
巫师们把萨巴克之冠藏了起来……
The wizards hid the Crown of Sabbac...
样它就不会再落入人类之手
so that it would never again fall into the hands of man.
捍卫者从此也杳无音讯
And the Champion was never heard from again.
坎达克，现今
KHANDAQ, PRESENT DAY
现在，坎达克被国际雇佣兵占领
Today, Kahndaq is occupied by international mercenaries,
国际帮是一系列外国入侵者中的最新
the Intergang, the latest in a series of foreign invaders.
但传说说过，只要坎达克最需要捍卫者的时候，
But legend says, whenever Kahndaq needs him most,
他就会回来解放坎达克人民
the Champion will return to restore freedom to the people.
但等待太久，太久了
It has been a long, long wait.
让我看看你的证件
Show me your papers.
国际帮5区检查点-北白田
INTERGANG CHECKPOINT Sector 5 - North Shiruta
准备好你的证件
Have your documentation ready.
这是我们仨的证件
It's all our three documents, yeah?
照片略丑，是女朋友和我分手后拍的
Don't judge the picture, it's after my girlfriend broke up with me.
打开后备厢，我需要看看里面
Open the back. Need a look inside.
看吧，没上锁，伙计
Yeah, it's unlocked, man.
只是一堆旧电视 -我是电工
It's just a bunch of old TVs. I'm an electrician.
看路！ 你知道规矩，退到队伍后面去
Watch where you're going. You know the drill, back of the line.
拜托，你每天都见到我
Come on, man, you see me every day.
我每天都和你说，只要它有轮子，那它就是交通工具
And every day I tell ya, if it's got wheels, it's a vehicle.
退到队伍后面去，伙计
Back of the line, mate.
你不是我的伙计
You're not my mate.
我现在心情不好，走吧，快滚
I'm heartbroken. Now, go on, piss off.
不，你才是从地球的另一端
No, what you are is a neo-imperialist enforcer,
新帝国执法者
from halfway around the world,
被派来窃取我国的资源，
sent here to steal my country's natural resources,
开采我们圣地的矿源，污染我们的水源，
strip-mine our sacred lands, pollute our water,
掠夺我们的国宝，让我们整天排队等候
oppress our heritage, and make us wait in lines all day.
嘿，老大 -我可以走吗?
Hey, boss man. Can I go?
走吧，离开这里
Go on, get out of here.
是的,是的
Yeah, yeah.
拘留
DETAIN
阿德里亚娜 安全了
Adrianna, we're clear.
坎达克对我们来说不再安全了
Kahndaq isn't safe for us anymore.
先把皇冠转移了 再来担心我们安不安全吧
Let's just move the crown first, and then we can worry about safe.
国际帮的人一直在监视我
I got Intergang watching my house.
我放弃我在大学的工作 还搬了四次家
I gave up my job at the university and moved four times.
但这并不意味着我要背弃我的国家
It doesn't mean I'm gonna abandon my country.
我想说的是 没人能永远比他们快上一步
I'm just saying, no one stays a step ahead of them forever.
这次我们已经等不到事情缓和下来了
We can't wait for things to cool down this time.
如果我猜得没错的话 他们很快就能找到皇冠了
If I'm right, they're days away from finding it.
-你在做什么  -我要跟你一起去
What are you doing? - I want to come with you.
你知道有多危险 你不应该牵扯进来
You know it's too dangerous. You shouldn't have gotten involved.
我想帮你打败那帮混蛋
Come on, I want to help you beat those bastards.
阿德里亚娜 请把头低下
Adriana, keep your head down, please.
你想当英雄 是吗？ -是的
You want to be a hero, huh? - I do, yeah.
回家去 做你的作业
Go home, do your homework.
属于你的时代会来的 但不是现在 儿子
Your time will come one day, but not today, son.
走吧
Go.
走吧 孩子 你已经做的很棒了
Go, little man. You did good.
这东西在黑市上想必很贵吧
That would get you a fortune on the black market.
是真正的永恒金属吗？
Is that real Eternium?
给我们展示点魔法吧
Show us a little magic.
没法弄 还需要精炼
It doesn't work like that, it's unrefined.
大家都歇会吧
You guys should get some rest.
我以为国际帮已经控制所有遗迹了
I thought Intergang seized all the old relics.
嘿 得了吧 别这样
Hey, come on. Stop it.
我就是想知道她是怎么得到它的
I'm just curious how she got it.
我祖母留给我的
My grandmother gave it to me.
-她又是怎么得到它的  -这又不是什么博物馆藏品
How did she get it? - It's not a museum piece.
这是家族传承的
It's a family heirloom,
这东西造出来的时候 坎达克还是个自由的国度
going all the way back to the days when Kahndaq was free.
满意了吧
You happy now?
这故事不错
Cool story.
留给我的只有一件毛衣
And all I inherited was a sweater.
才不是呢 爸爸还把旧货车和秃头留给你了
That's not true. Baba left you his van, and his bald spot.
你要知道有的女人就是喜欢秃顶
You know, some women like a bald spot.
外面卷曲 可里面是光滑 懂么
Curly on the outside, smooth on the inside. You know?
你确定没问题吗
Are you sure about this?
我们发现的铭文镌刻得很清楚
The inscrptions we found are clear.
我对我的翻译也很有自信 山里好像有东西
And I'm positive about that translation. There is something inside that mountain.
如果真的是皇冠呢 我们要怎么办
What if it really is the crown? Then what?
这么强大的力量 谁能拥有它呢
It's a source of great power. Who gets to keep it?
没有人可以拥有 我们得把它藏到别的地方
No one. We hide it again someplace else.
如果有必要的话还得离开国内 不管是谁 拥有它都太危险了
Get it out of the country if we have to. It is too dangerous for anyone to have.
就这样吗
This is it?
还没完呢
Not yet.
-你来吗  -我膝盖不行 留在这望风
Are you coming? - Bad knee. I'll keep watch.
这边 快到了
This way. Almost there.
"人们生来就有魔法天赋
"Men were given the gift of magic,
但内心却极容易被腐蚀"
but their hearts were too easily corrupted."
接着念
Keep reading.
"终极能量从地上被放逐 并藏在了...这里"
"The ultimate power was banished from the earth and hidden... here."
直到现在
Until now.
沙巴克之冠在这座山里安全存放了五千年
This mountain has kept the Crown of Sabbac safe for 5,000 years.
我们真的确定带走它没问题吗
We're 100 percent, totally, no take-backs certain that we want to move it?
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
伊斯梅尔哪去了?
What happened to Ishmael?
别担心 我去找他
Great. Don't worry, I'll find him.
萨密尔？
Samir?
萨密尔 怎么了？
Samir, what happened?
你说什么？
What?
我听不清 你说什么？
I can't hear you. What are you saying?
不想和他一样就别动
Don't move. Unless you want to join your mate.
别动
Stay where you are.
好吧 好吧
Oh, hey. Oh, hey. Hey...
"往回走"
"Turn back."
上面就是这么写的 对吧？
That's what it says, no?
没错
Yes.
萨密尔呢？
Where is Samir?
幽闭恐惧症 他去呼吸点新鲜空气
Claustrophobic. Needed some air.
-这么走能找到皇冠吧？  -我觉得是
Is this the way to the crown? - I think so.
这是一座坟墓
It's a tomb.
"不要提及他的力量
"Speak not his power,
让他永远沉睡下去"特斯·亚当
so he may suffer a dreamless sleep for all eternity" Teth Adam.
那位成为捍卫者 打败了国王的奴隶
The slave who became champion and defeated the king.
传说是真的
The legend was true.
坎达克曾经有过一位英雄
Kahndaq... really did have a hero once.
如果他真的是英雄 为什么他们把他埋在这？
If he was such a hero, why'd they bury him down here?
皇冠
The crown.
结束了
It's over.
把皇冠给我
Now, give me the crown.
快跑，艾迪，快跑
Run, Addy. Run.
别打了
Hold fire.
别打到皇冠 抓住她
Don't hit the crown. Get her.
-快点  -包抄她
Go. Move. - Circle around.
蹲下
Get down.
和你的哥哥说再见吧
Say goodbye to your brother.
五
In five...
四
four...
三
three...
二
two...
一
one...
我在这
I'm over here.
你怎么能让他数到一？
One? You let them get to one?
还有遗言吗？
Any last words?
请转告我儿子
Please tell my son...
"凡人中的至强者
"Mightiest of mortals...
诸神之神
god of gods,
六位永生长者名为..."
Six Immortal Elders by name..."
什么？
What?
"沙赞"
"Shazam."
那是谁？
Who the hell is that?
我告诉你你也不会信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
去看看他
Check him out.
老板让你去
Boss say you go.
长官说该你了
Chief say your turn.
伙计 让我看到你的双手
Hey, amigo. Let me see your hands.
开火
Open fire.
你的魔法太弱了
Your magic is weak.
快走快走
Go. Go.
我们急需后援 把所有后援都叫来
We need immediate backup. Send everything you've got.
伊斯梅尔|
Ishmael.
伊斯梅尔
-我们走  -这已经是我的极限了
Let's go. - This is as fast as I can go.
萨密尔 怎么了?
Samir. What happened?
还能发生什么
What didn't happen.
萨密尔从悬崖上摔了下来
Samir fell off of a cliff.
我被枪指着脑袋
I had a gun to my head.
伊斯梅尔被埋在山底下
Ishmael is buried under a mountain.
结果你召唤了一个会飞会魔法的人 结果呢？
And you summoned some flying magic man. All for what?
啥都没有?
Nothing.
也不是全无收获
Not for nothing.
开火
Light him up.
靠 他是从哪冒出来的
Shit. Where the hell did he come from?
旋翼废了 快走
Rotor out. Go. Go.
我没办法保持高度
I can't maintain altitude.
哦，靠
Oh, shit.
停，停车
Stop. Stop the van.
注意身后
Behind you.
他徒手接了个火箭弹？
Did he just catch a rocket?
上帝保佑 我们再也不会见到他了
God willing, we won't see him again.
等等 你干嘛？
Wait. Hey. Hey. What are you doing?
别碰他 他身上都是闪电
Don't touch him, he's made of lightning.
你说得对
Good point.
那你来 你是电工
You get him, you're the electrician.
猛禽小队 请回答
Raptor team, come in.
你们在什么方位？
What's your status?
帮帮我
Help me.
我让你装得像一点 没让你打我脸
I told you to make it look real, not punch me in the face.
猛禽小队 请回答 你们在什么位置？
Raptor team, come in. What is your status?
位置是在一群死人边上
Status is that everyone is dead.
伊斯梅尔 是你吗？发生什么了？
Ishmael, is that you? What happened?
在这等着我们的不只是皇冠
The crown wasn't the only thing waiting for us down here.
-你得手了吗？  -没有 但我知道谁拿了
Do you have it? - No. But I know who does.
收到 我们现在就去你那里
Copy that. We're en route to your location.
我们需要立即增援 请派出所有人手
We need immediate backup. Send everything you've got.
几个世纪以来人们试图开采出这种稀有神奇的矿物
This rare, magical mineral has been mined for centuries...
据报道一块永恒金属发生爆炸 具体原因尚不清楚
...reports of an Eternium blast. It is unknown who or why...
大量士兵阵亡 我们将持续为您报道
...has decimated a number of troops. We are waiting on...
一名身份不明的男子 他不知为何竟能控制
...an unidentified male. This being is somehow able to harness...
你怎么看？
What do you think?
我觉得该把这个惹是生非的家伙关起来
I think this loose cannon needs to be locked down...
不能让他伤害无辜的人
before innocent people start getting hurt.
哦 对了 也祝你早安
Oh, and good mornig to you, too.
闭嘴吧 卡特
Shove it up your ass, Carter.
他已经沉睡了五千年
He's been asleep for 5,000 years.
刚醒肯定不适应
He'll be disoriented at first.
一旦他适应了 就更难抓他了
The longer he has to adapt, the harder it will be to take him down.
三十分钟后出发
Wheels up in 30.
还有谁？
Who's on the team?
您好 请说出姓名以确认身份
Welcome. Please state your name for identification.
你好 我是玛克辛·亨克尔 我是来见霍尔先生的
Hi. I'm Maxine Hunkel. I'm here to see Mr Hall.
已确认 您好 玛克辛
Confirmed. Welcome, Maxine.
谢谢
Thanks.
玛克辛·亨克尔 “飓风”
Maxine Hunkel, aka Cyclone.
能掌控风 也是电脑高手 聪明绝顶
Wind manipulation powers, computer skills, smart as hell.
可以说就是一个智商167的“飓风”
Basically a tornado with a 167 IQ.
感觉很厉害的亚子
Sounds delightful.
但请你告诉我还有没有更能打的
But please tell me you found someone who can pack a punch.
当然 原子粉碎者闪亮登场
That's where Atom Smasher comes in.
阿尔·罗斯坦 初代原子粉碎者的侄子
Al Rothstein, nephew to the original Atom Smasher.
他继承了叔叔的神力
He inherited his uncle's powers.
我的战服怎么样？好看吗？
How's my suit? Does it fit?
好看 很完美 再次谢谢你借给我
No, yeah. It's perfect. Thank you again for letting me borrow it.
我从小就很关注你
You know, I used to watch you all the time as a kid?
我非常想要你这套衣服
This is literally the only thing that I'd ever wanted in my...
可别弄坏了
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Don't let anything happen to it.
这可是中古品
It's Vintage.
你自己也小心
And don't let anything happen to you, either.
别做傻事 听卡特安排
Don't do anything crazy. You listen to Carter.
我不会丢你脸的 阿尔叔叔 我保证
I'm gonna make you proud, Uncle Al. I promise.
他们看着就像菜鸟
They seem green.
所以我还叫了肯特
That's why I called in Kent.
他有段时间没出过任务了
Кent's been out of action for a little while,
但这次行动不能没有他
but I can't do this without him.
要用魔法打败魔法 这个人可是有着神一般的法力
Takes magic to fight magic and the man's got nearly god-level powers.
感觉还是实力悬殊 你确定他们能把他拿下？
It might take a lot than that. Are you sure they can take him?
沃勒 你只需要找一间能关住他的牢房
Waller, you find us a cell that can hold him...
其余的就交给我们吧
we'll take care of the rest.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
这下有得玩了
This is gonna be fun.
我们到了 先生
We're here, sir.
好的
Oh, right.
我又走神了？
Was I staring again?
也就半个小时吧 先生
Only half an hour or so, sir.
下次你可以按喇叭叫醒我
Maybe next time, honk the horn.
好的 先生
Of course, sir.
这次任务是什么？
So what's the op?
我们要去坎达克
We're headed to Kahndaq to apprehend and contain...
抓一个A级超能坏蛋
a Class-A rogue metahuman.
我没带护照
I didn't bring passport.
用不着护照 我们可是正义协会的一员
We don't need passports. We're the Justice Society.
这全都是N金属做的？
Is this entirely made out of Nth metal?
哪怕是螺丝都是 坚不可摧
Everyting down to the screws. Completely indestructible.
找我的话就来驾驶舱
I'll be in the cockpit if you need me.
太酷了 你有什么零嘴么？
It's pretty cool. You got any snacks?
吃饱了才有力气去打怪嘛
It takes a lot of energy to smash atoms.
给你
Here.
哦 谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
对了 我叫阿尔
I'm Al, by the way.
我叫玛克辛
Мaxine.
你的超能力是什么？
What do you do?
呼风唤雨 你呢？
Wind. You?
我可以长个
I grow.
帅
Сool.
没事 我可以再买一个
Don't worry about that. I can get another one.
虽然我妈妈不是医生 但你可能需要处理下...
My mom's not much of a doctor, but you should probably leave th...
或者像这样
Or do that.
我知道你现在一下子没法接受这么多
I know you have a lot to catch up on.
但我想我们可以互相帮助
But, I was thinking we could help each other.
-走开  -对了 我叫阿蒙
Мove. - I'm Amon, by the way.
我没问你的名字
I didn't ask for your name.
你是特斯·亚当 对吗？坎达克的每个人都知道你的历史
You're Teth Adam, right? Everyone in Kahndaq knows your story.
我说了 走开
I said move.
我妈妈说你在沙漠里干掉了一群国际帮的人
My mom said you took out a bunch of Intergang soldiers in the desert.
因为他们挡我的路
Because they wouldn't move out of my way.
所以你真的能飞 还能挡住子弹 这对我的计划很重要
So you can really fly and stop bullets, 'cause that's really crucial to my plan.
真的是你挡住那些子弹的吗 还是这身制服？
And is it really you stopping the bullets or is it the suit?
等等 你最快的速度是多快？
Wait, what's your top speed?
我知道你的速度很快 但是有多快？像闪电侠一样快吗？
I'm sure you're fast, but how fast? Like Flash fast?
等等 你们那时候不会没有镜子吧？
Wait, did you not have mirrors back then?
我相信这五千年来确实改变了很多
Wow, I guess a lot does change in 5,000 years.
五千年？
Five thousand years?
是的 我妈妈将你唤醒之前
Yeah, that's how long you were in the tomb.
你确实在坟墓里待了这么久
Until my mom woke you up.
所以确认一下，你能挡住子弹，还能飞
So you've got stopping bullets, check; flying, check;
还能点火 刚刚亲眼确认过了
and lighting thing, that's a big check.
我不认识这个地方
I don't know this place.
这是你的家
This is your home.
那我的家就不在了
Then my home is gone.
皇冠怎么了？
What happened to the crown?
太多了？
Too much?
你知道它被恶魔诅咒了 对吧
You know it's cursed with demons, right?
"生命的本质就是通往死亡的路"
"Life is the... only path to death."
别说废话
No shit.
特斯·亚当是坎达克战乱时代的英雄"
"Teth Adam was a Bronze Age Kahndaqi demi-god."
"他在大约公元前2600年打败了阿克顿王"
"He defeated King Ahk-Ton in approximately 2,600 BC."
这里 这是你 看到了吗
There. That's you. See?
这是他们为你建造的雕像 现在你回来了
That's the statue they built of you. And now you're back.
自从你离开后
Our country's been oppressed by one invader...
我们的国土长期遭到侵略
after another over since you left.
我是想说 坎达克还没有得到自由
My point is, Kahndaq still isn't free.
我们现在真的需要一个超级英雄
We could really use a superhero right about now.
我不是英雄
I'm no hero.
怎么可能？
What?
超人 蝙蝠侠 海王... -你比他们都厉害
Superman, Batman, Aquaman... You're way more stacked than any of them.
他们不会来坎达克救我们
And they're not coming to Kahndaq to save us.
但你可以凭一己之力干掉国际帮
But you could stop Intergang all by yourself,
就像你对阿克顿王那样
just like you did King Ahk-Ton.
你是我们唯一的希望
You're our only hope.
巫师
Wizards.
别担心 我能修好
I can fix it. Don't worry.
我不是巫师
I'm not a wizard.
嘿 妈妈 他醒了
Hey, Mom. He's awake.
我警告过你别进房间
I told you not to go in your room.
当时是你念的咒语
It was you who spoke.
你唤醒了我
You woke me.
我别无选择 要是没成功我就死了
I didn't have a choice. I'd be dead if it hadn't worked.
在我墓里的那些人 是你的敌人吗？
The men in my tomb, they were your enemies?
那你的敌人已经败了
Then your enemies are vanquished,
他们会陷入永久沉睡的诅咒
condemned to the eternal sleep of the damned.
其实 我们还有很多敌人需要消灭
Actually, we still have a lot of enemies that need vanquishing.
那就毁灭他们
Then destroy them.
国际帮有枪和飞车 还有永恒金属做的火箭
Intergang have guns and flybikes and Eternium rockets.
而我们只有母爱
We have my mom.
证明你的力量 摧毁你的敌人和他所关心的一切
Prove your strength. Destroy your enemy and all he cares about.
让他求饶 但直到他生命的最后一刻都决不让他得到救赎
Make him beg for mercy, but deny it until his final breath.
-有趣  -好吧
Interesting, okay?
我很感谢你对我的帮助
I appreciate what you did to for me,
但我不希望你教我儿子使用暴力
but I do not want you teaching my son violence.
我理解 你想让他的父亲教他使用暴力
I understand. You want his father to teach him violence.
-恶心 他是我弟弟  -她是我姐姐
Gross, that's my brother. - That's my sister.
-他父亲死了  -我很抱歉
His father's dead. - I'm sorry.
那你想让谁教他功夫？
Who do you want to teach him violence then?
对呀 妈妈 你想让谁教我使用功夫呢？
Yeah, Mom. Who do you want to teach me violence?
谁都不行
No one.
我想要一个能从国际帮那里解放坎达克的捍卫者
I want a champion to help free Kahndaq from Intergang.
拜托你 帮帮我们
Please, help us.
等等，等一下
Wait. Wait.
-你要去哪儿？  -我不应该在这里
Where are you going? - I shouldn't be here.
你对我们没有一点忠诚感吗
You don't feel any loyalty to us at all?
并没有
Not really, no.
你不了解真实的情况
You're not seeing the full possibilities here.
我不知道在上古时代是什么样
I don't know what is was like in ancient times,
但是在这个时代 有超能力是一件非常了不起的事
but having superpowers is kind of a big deal in our world.
也许你可以理一下制服 配个披风 改名换姓
Maybe clean up your outfit a little bit, get a cape, change your name.
特斯·亚当是个有力的名字
Teth Adam is a very strong name.
有点过时了 而且你肯定需要加一句口号
It's a little outdated. And you definitely need a catchphrase.
就是那种在你干掉坏人之前
Something blackout bad-ass to say,
就能唬住他们的话
right before you absolutely cook some dude.
我不在死人身上浪费口舌
I don't waste words on the dead.
好吧 差不多意思 就是要更好记一点
Well, yeah, kind of like that, but more catchy.
我想想 比如说"告诉他们是黑衣人送你来的"
I was thinking, like, "Tell them the Man in the Black sent you."
-他们？  -就是神啊 恶魔啥的
Them? - You know, gods, demons...
死后迎接我们的人
Whoever's waiting for us in the afterlife.
而且你的制服是黑色的 我们得好好利用这一点
And you wear a lot of black, so we should really lean into that.
我的意思是 你能出名
My point is, you could be famous.
上杂志 印在午餐盒上 做成电子游戏
Magazines, lunch boxes, video games.
超级英雄产业可值不少钱
And the superhero industrial complex is worth a lot of money.
我吃饭不需要盒子
I don't need a box for my lunch.
所有你认识的人都死了
Anyone you've ever known is dead.
你还要做什么？
What else are you gonna do?
等等 你要去哪？
Wait. Where are you going?
沃勒还需要点时间来完成档案
Waller's file needs a bit to be desired.
直到昨天下午之前 我们还以为这些神话故事大多是虚构的
Most of this was considered a myth until yesterday afternoon.
他是坏人 肯特 还有什么想知道的吗？
He's a bad man, Kent. What else do you need to know?
如果你和我一样预见过许多截然不同的未来
When you've seen as many different futures as I have,
你就不会这么坚决了
you cease to believe in absolutes.
你笑什么？
What are you laughing at?
我没在笑 发傻而已
I'm not laughing. That was a smirk.
我知道 你笑起来就这样
I know. That's how you laugh.
真怀念你讲这种哔哔赖赖的屁话的日子
I've missed having you around to spout old cryptic shit like that.
我也同样怀念你从来不把我当回事的日子
Almost as much as I've missed having you around to ignore all my advice.
卡特
Carter...
这个计划可不太妙
This is not a very good plan.
嗯哼
Yeah, well...
坏计划总好过没计划
A bad plan is better than no plan at all.
要是还有其他办法就好了
If only there were a third option.
如果是我 我不会碰它的
I wouldn't touch that if I was you.
为什么？
Why not?
因为那个头盔来自另一颗星球
'Cause that helmet is from another planet.
它已经有上百万年的历史了
It's millions of years old.
只有被选中的人才能触碰
It chooses who it lets touch it.
-比如肯特？  -没错
Like Kent? - Yeah.
而且 肯特在戴上头盔的时候处于被占据的状态
Like, Kent is leterally possessed when he puts it on.
那要是我就是要去碰它呢
What happens if I touch it anyway?
会感到非常恐怖这样的吗
Soul crushing terror? Or... something.
那最好还是盖条毛巾吧
So we should probably put a towel on it, right?
来吧
Coming up on it.
五秒后准备就绪
Ready stations in five.
嘿 为什么这位亚当兄弟火气这么大
Hey, why is this Adam dude so pissed off?
他可不是什么兄弟
He's not some dude.
他是大规模杀伤性武器
He's a weapon of mass destruction.
你没必要举手
You don't have to raise your hand.
问题是：如果他非常强大 我们怎么阻止他
Question: if he's so powerful, how are we supposed to stop him?
如果我们能让他说出"沙赞"这个词
If we can get him to say the word, "Shazam,"
特斯·亚当就会失去他的力量
Teth Adam will lose his power.
既然他已经沉睡了千年之久
And we're hoping since he's had a few thousand years to sleep it off,
我们希望能与他平和的讨论一下 他要如何在现代社会中生存
we can peacefully negotiate the terms of his existence.
从你给我们的录像看来
From the footage you showed us,
他可不像是那种会跟你平和讨论的人
he doesn't really seem like a "peacefully negotiate" kind of guy.
正确
Correct.
注意了
Look alive.
我们到了
We're here.
正在进入坎达克领空
ENTERING KAHNDAQI AIRSPACE
原谅我
Forgive me.
致全体国际帮士兵
This is a message for all Intergang soldiers.
坎达克现在也正式有拥有自己的超级英雄了
Kahndaq has its own official superhero now.
特斯·亚当
Тeth Adam.
求你了
Please.
他在那 闪开
There he is. Move.
-特斯·亚当  -闪开
Тeth Adam. - Move.
特斯·亚当
Тeth Adam...
现在谁来救你呢 小子
Who's gonna save you now, mate?
那座雕像？
The statue?
他是我儿子
That's my son.
他还小 做事糊里糊涂的
He's just a boy. He doesn't know what he's doing.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
等等 我认识你
Hang on. I recognize you.
皇冠在哪？
Where is the crown?
走
Let's go.
你本可以再早点现身的 当然已经很酷啦
You could've showed up a bit sooner. But that was dope.
我们需要支援
We need backup down here.
告诉他们是黑衣人送你来的
Tell them the Man in Black sent you.
对 就这样 但别对我说 对那些坏蛋说
Well, yes, but not to me. Say it to the bad guys.
而且是在你杀了他们之前说
But before you zap them.
-先口号 后开杀  -没错
Catchphrase, then kill. - Yes.
他就在这
He's here.
你感知到他了？
You sense his presence?
不是
No.
但我猜全坎达克也只有他能做出这种事
I assume he's the only person in Kahndaq that can do that.
肯特和我打头阵 听着
Fate and I'll take the lead. Listen.
现在 你们呆在这 等我们叫你们
Now, you two hang back 'til we call you.
我们是铁砧板 你们是锤子 你们已经准备好了
We're the anvil, you're the hammer. You're ready.
他刚刚把...
He just dropped the...
靠
Shit.
做好准备
Be prepared.
在你后面
Behind you.
-让我们来杀了他们吧  -你是不是疯了
Let us be.
我不知道他们犯了什么罪
I don't know their crimes,
但无论如何 这些人都得走正当程序
but whatever they are, these men should face due process.
那就让神来审判吧
Then let the gods make their judgment.
-太棒了  -干得漂亮
Yeah. - Yeah.
你们看起来不像是国际帮的人
You don't look like an Intergang.
我们是正义协会的成员
We're the Justice Society.
我们的任务就是守护世界稳定
Our mission is to protect global stability.
我们来到这里是为了让坎达克恢复和平
We're here to restore peace to Kahndaq.
必要的话我们会采用武力对抗
And we will use force if necessary.
武力永远必要
Force is always necessary.
特斯·亚当
Teth Adam.
我们知道你是谁 也知晓你的能力
We know who you are and what you are capable of.
但是在这个人类的世界 你已经没有容身之地了
There's no place for you in the world of man.
你有两个选择 要么臣服 要么死
You have two choices: kneel or die.
我死前一直是一名奴隶
I was a slave until I died.
后来我重生为神
Then I was reborn a god.
我永不臣服
I kneel before no one.
肯特 让他分心
Fate, give me a distraction.
说一声"沙赞"我们就都能回家了
Just say, "Shazam." We all go home.
我四海为家
I don't have a home.
瞧瞧这一身 有点酷
Look at that suit. It's cool.
谢谢 你的衣服也很帅
Thanks. You, too.
谢谢你 这是我叔叔传给我的
Thank you. It was a hand-me-down. It was from my uncle.
-鹰侠从不放弃 是吧  -对
Hawkman just does not give up, does he? - Nope.
阿蒙 你到哪儿去 等一下
Amon, where are you going? Wait.
我想帮帮他
To help him.
旋风 粉碎者 轮到你们了
Cyclone, Smasher, now is your time.
让大风呼啸起来吧
Let's roll.
你干嘛呢 嘿
What are you doing? Hey.
不要
No.
我马上就来
I'll be right there.
你竟然有沙巴克之冠
You have the Crown of Sabbac.
我抓不住他了
I can't hold him much longer.
起来
Move.
我来了 我已经到了
I'm coming. I'm zeroing in on your location.
我抓住他了 朋友们 我抓到他了
I got him. Guys, I got him.
是我 阿尔 以防你认不出来我
It's me, Al. In case you didn't recognize me.
你变化有点大 我的手都有点抓不住你了
There's something different about you. Can't quite put my finger on it.
那可能是因为我现在已经有六层楼高了吧
You know, it's probably because I'm six stories tall now.
但是你...你像龙卷风一样
But you... You're like a tornado.
我觉得你们俩干的非常好
I thought the two of you did great work.
第一次出场...厉害
First time out... Bravo.
谢谢 我是说 我刚刚有点迷路了
Thanks. I mean, I got a little turned around back there,
但是 这一切都结束了 不是吗
but, it all worked out, right?
你说的太他妈对了
You're damn right it did.
希望沃勒已经为他准备好牢房了
Let's hope Waller has that cell ready for him.
你们想让我的手一直放在这儿 是吗
You want me to keep my hand here, right?
你最好别让他起来
You'd better not let him up.
我该怎么办 兄弟们
What do I do? Guys?
捍卫者不朽 捍卫者永存
Long live the Champion. Long live the Champion.
捍卫者不朽
Long live the Champion.
捍卫者永存
嗯 他还在喘气儿呢
Yeah, he's definitely still breathing.
捍卫者不朽 捍卫者永存
Long live the Champion. Long live the Champion.
-你要到哪里去  -我们得追上他
Where are you going? We need to go after him.
我们还不够强大
We're not strong enough.
是么 那或许下次在我们被揍得屁滚尿流之前
Oh, well, maybe next time use your powers of prediction...
你能用一下你预言未来的能力
to figure that out before we gor our asses kicked.
我已经在预言了
I'm working on it.
小姐
Miss?
不好意思 你介意我看一下你的包包吗
Excuse me, you mind if I look in your bag?
嗯 我介意
Yes, I do mind.
你搞什么鬼呢 肯特
Where are you going with this, Kent?
她拿到了沙巴克之冠|
She's got the Crown of Sabbac.
这会酿成一场灾难 我们不能再给他机会让他重振旗鼓了
One catastrophe at a time. We can't give him a chance to regroup.
他已经在宫殿里面了
He's been spotted entering the palace.
他肯定不是去那里投降的
It safe to say he's not going there to surrender.
为什么你们要让特斯·亚当臣服
Why do you want Teth Adam to surrender?
他是坎达克的捍卫者 你们又是何方神圣
He's the Champion of Kahndaq? Who are you?
正义协会
The Justice Society?
我们已经在军事占领下生活了二十七年
We have been living under military occupation for 27 years,
却从来没见过你们
and never seen you before.
当国际帮入侵我们的国家时 肆意榨取我们的资源 你们没有来
You didn't come when Intergang invaded our country,
当他们杀害我丈夫的时候 你们没有出现
when they stole our resources and killed my husband.
如今 我们终于有了属于我们自己的英雄
But now, we finally have our own hero...
你们却在这个时候飞下来"拯救"我们？
and you decide to fly down here and save us?
谢了 但是...我们已经被保护得很好了
Thank you, but... we're covered.
你们还是去别的地方维护国家稳定吧
Go and protect inernational stability someplace else.
噢 还有 我可没有皇冠
Oh, and second, I don't have the crown.
我来给你说说清楚吧
Let me spell it out for you.
特斯·亚当不可能成为坎达克的捍卫者 因为他并不是英雄
Teth Adam can't be Kahndaq's champion because he is not a hero.
把这句话...
Tell that...
告诉那些刚刚被他解救的人吧
to all the people he just liberated.
我知道这件事看上去很奇怪 真的
I know what this looks like. I do.
但我可以向你保证...
But I can assure you that my t...
真是不好意思 这个贵吗？
I am so sorry. Was that expensive?
我得和你好好聊聊 等我们回到飞船上...
Me and you. When we get back to the ship...
-是的 长官  -必须聊聊了
Yes, sir. - Me and you.
我...
I...
请让我们看看皇冠好吗？
Can we please just see the crown?
皇冠不在我这
I don't have it.
我们没时间了
We don't have time for this.
先去追特斯·亚当 再来找皇冠
Teth Adam first, then the crown.
你们在这里没有任何权力 特斯·亚当什么也没做过...
You don't have any authority here. Teth Adam has done nothing...
特斯·亚当不是你想象中的那个人
Teth Adam is not who you think he is.
你怎么知道？
And how whould you know?
我们能够看到几个世纪以来一直秘密封存的古代文献
We have access to ancient texts that have been kept secret for centuries.
所以这些文献里记载了什么呢？
And what exactly do these supposed ancient texts say?
记载了坎达克差点因为他的暴行而毁于一旦
They say that his rage nearly destroyed Kahndaq.
我们大老远飞到这就是为了阻止这种事再次发生
And we flew all the way over here to stop it from happening again.
你要一个人进去吗？你确定吗？
You want to go in there alone? Are you sure?
你要是想去和特斯·亚当再打一架 随便你
You want to go in and fight Teth Adam again, be my guest.
但你如果想要和平地解决问题
But if you actually want to resolve things peacefully,
而不是毁掉这座城市的话 我是你唯一的机会
without destroying the rest of my city, I'm your only shot.
你把侵略者带来了
You brought the invaders with you.
他们只是想和你说几句话
They only want to talk.
随便他们说什么 反正我不会听
They can talk. I won't listen.
我小时候 我祖母给我讲过一个故事
When I was a little girl, my grandmother told me the story...
这个故事是关于捍卫者来到坎达克
of how the Champion came to this exact spot...
打败阿克顿王 并解放被他奴役的子民们
to free the enslaved people of Kahndaq by defeating King Ahk-Ton in battle.
但是正义协会的成员说 事实并非如此
But according to the Justice Society, that's not really what happened.
他们说你并不是来寻求正义的
They say that you didn't come here to seek justice.
快点
Hurry.
给我
Give it to me.
而是来复仇的
That you came to exact revenge.
在你的愤怒之下...
And in your anger...
别杀我 你要什么我都给你
Don't kill me. I can give you anything you want.
这就是我想要的
This is what I want.
...你的力量变得越来越强大 直到无法控制
...your power grew until it became uncontrollable.
巫师议会认为
And the Council of Wizards was forced to deem you unworthy...
你配不上被赐予的力量
of the gifts that you were granted.
因为我们鲁莽的选择...
We have chosen recklessly...
人类付出了惨痛的代价
and humanity has paid the price.
现在 特斯·亚当...
And now, Teth Adam...
你也必须付出代价
you must pay.
我打开的不是你的坟墓 对吗
It wasn't your tomb that I opened, was it?
那是你的监狱
It was your prison.
如今这里还塑着你的雕像
And now there's a statue of you.
人们希望有一天坎达克的捍卫者能回来
Out of the hope that someday Kahndaq's champion would return.
但这是建立在谎言之上的 对吗
But it's built on a lie, isn't it.
我从没说过我是英雄
I never said I was a hero.
我从来没有自称过什么
I never claimed to be anything.
你或许不是英雄
You may not have been a hero.
但不代表你现在不能成为英雄
But that doesn't mean that you can't be one now.
我会听听他们的说法
I will hear them out.
但如果他们选择开战 就是他们自己找死
But if they choose to fight, they choose to die.
卡里姆舅舅
Uncle Karim.
难以置信 你坐在这看电视的时候
I can't believe you're sitting around watching TV...
外面发生了多么惊天动地的...
when the most epic day ever is...
在这屋呢 小伙子
In here, little man.
伊斯梅尔 妈妈说你被埋在坟墓里了
Ishmael. My mom said you got buried in the tomb.
有趣的是 并没有
Funny story, he didn't.
阿德里亚娜在哪里
Where's Adrianna?
-她还在广场...  -我们现在应该去帮她
She's back at the square... - We should go bail her out right now.
但她让我回来就是为了确保皇冠的安全
But she's the one who sent me home to make sure the crown's safe.
皇冠很安全好吗 肯定在其他什么地方
It is safe, okay? Somewhere else.
反正不在这 我们... 好吧...
Definitely not here. Let... Okay...
-把包放下  -你要干什么
Put the bag down. - What are you doing?
退后 立刻把包放下
Back away. Put the bag down, now.
把包给他 把包给他
Give him the bag. Give hime the bag.
很好 退后
Very good. Back away.
-退后  -行 我...
Back away. - Oké. I'm...
一切都会好起来的 小伙子
It's all going to be okay, little man.
我来给你上节历史课吧
Let me teach you some history that you've never learned...
你妈的课堂里可从来没有教过哦
in one of your mother's classes.
曾经我们有一位强大的国王
When we had a powerful king,
那时坎达克拥有比自由更美好的东西
Kahndaq used to be something much better than free.
今这里曾一度辉煌
It used to be great.
快跑 阿蒙
Run, Amon, run.
派人搜查大楼 我没抓到那孩子 他带着皇冠跑了
Crash the building. I lost the kid. He has the crown.
我们来协商让你和平投降的条件
We're here to negotoiate the terms of your peaceful surrender.
我不是为了和平而来 而且也不会投降
I'm not peaceful. Nor do I surrender.
你的能力为你带来了什么？不过是让你徒增烦恼罢了
What have your powers ever given to you? Nothing but heartache.
你不会明白的
You have no idea.
你为什么非要这么难为我们？
Then why are you making this hard on us?
你我都心知肚明 你根本不该来这里
We both know you're not supposed to be here.
不该来这里的人是你们
It is you who is not supposed to be here.
我希望你们都离开坎达克 不要再回来
I want you all to leave Kahndaq and never return.
乐意至极 但前提是你要同我们一起走
Gladly, with you as our prisoner.
不如先让我把你那对小翅膀扯掉怎么样
How 'bout I rip you little wings off instead?
-你倒来试试看  -好了 战斗并不能解决实质问题
I'd like to see you try. - Okay, more fighting won't solve this.
-我可不这么觉得  -我也是
I disagree. - Me, too.
看来大家都找到共同点了
Looks like we found common ground.
这场战斗只会以一种方式结束
This can only end one way.
-妈妈？  -阿蒙
Мom? - Amon.
我回家发现伊斯梅尔坐在厨房里
I got home and Ishmael was in the kitchen.
伊斯梅尔已经死了
Ishmael's dead.
他没死 卡里姆舅舅还中枪了 他是来拿皇冠的
No, he shot Uncle Karim, and he's after the crown.
地面部队...
Ground forces...
我正在楼里躲着 国际帮的人也在这里
I'm hiding in our building, and Intergang's here.
他们过来了
They're coming.
国际帮在追杀我的儿子
Intergang are after my son.
他们不想要你儿子 他们只想要沙巴克之冠
They don't want him, they want the Crown of Sabbac.
我知道你不是英雄
I know you're not a hero.
但你也不是恶魔 我不在乎别人怎么说你
But you're not a monster, either. I don't care what anyone says.
你在那个山洞里救了我
You saved me in that cave.
你根本不认识我 但你第一反应却是来救我
You didn't know me and your first instinct was to save me.
我恳求你 救救我的儿子
I'm begging you. Please, save my son.
搜查整座楼
Check the whole place clean.
守好所有进出口
Cover all access points.
继续搜索
Keep looking.
这里没人
Area's clear.
他在那里 抓住他
There. Take him.
快过去 他在那边
Right there, right there.
妈的...
Shit...
快追 快追
Move, move.
别开枪 我要活的
Don't shoot him, I need him.
无路可走了 孩子
End of the road, kid.
放开那个孩子
Release the child.
悉听尊便
Whatever you say.
太好了
Yes.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不过下次说话前 你最好先斟酌一下用词再开口
But maybe be more careful with your word choice next time.
对了 记得再说一下你的战斗口号
Оh. And remember your catchphrase.
该走了 阿蒙
Time to go, Amon.
-皇冠在哪？  -什么皇冠？
Where's the crown? - What crown?
-你想逞能是吗？  -我想让你下地狱
You want to be brave, eh? - I want you to go to hell.
我还正想去呢 小伙子 我们得走了 快进去
That's the plan, little man. We'er gonna go for a ride. Come one.
快放下我 放下我
Put me down. Put me down.
下次说话前 你最好先斟酌一下用词再开口
You should really be more careful with your word choice next time.
告诉他们是黑衣人...
And tell them that the Man in Black...
他就在我身后 人们都到哪去了？
He's right behind me. Where the hell is everybody?
妈妈？
Mom?
阿蒙 你在哪？
Amon, where are you?
不不不 你说什么？
No, no, no, what?
我在他们的车上
I'm on one of their bikes.
什么车？
What bikes?
阿蒙
Amon.
能听到我说话吗？
Can you hear me?
妈妈 我没事
Mom, I'm okay.
妈的
Shit.
激活红外功能
Activate infrared.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我在找那个孩子
Searching for the child.
不 你在杀害人类
No, you're murdering people.
那我还能怎么找？
How else do I find the child?
我可以帮你 但你不能再随意杀人了
I can help you, but no more extrajudicial killings.
我不需要你的帮助
I don't need any help.
]z 粉碎者 旋风 你俩还等什么？
Smasher, Cyclone. What are you waiting for?
-行了 咱们走吧  -好的
Come on, let's go. - Okay.
没问题 我可以的 数到三就跳
Okay. I got this. On the count of three.
1 2... 这感觉比上次高得多啊
One, two... This feels a lot higher than last time.
太吓人了
That was not cool.
哇喔 快停车
Whoa, slow down.
没事 我罩着你
I got you. I got you.
嘿 小心点兄弟 我差点打到你
Hey, careful, dude. I almost hit you.
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
面罩会挡住我的视野 这是我叔叔的
I don't really have peripheral vision in the mask. It's my uncle's.
我会重新找人裁制一下的
I'll get it tailored.
我和你这账先记下
Me and you.
明白
Roger that.
-你是谁？  -你可以叫我命运博士
Who are you? - Call me Dr. Fate.
我的伤还有救吗 医生？我要死了吗？
How bad is it, Doc? Am I dying?
我不是那种治病救人的医生
I'm not that kind of doctor.
但别担心 我能预见未来
But don't worry, I can see the future.
你不会这么死
This isn't how you're going to die.
那我会怎么死？
How do I die, then?
离电远点就好
Just stay away from electricity.
等等 什么 我可是电工
Wait, what? I'm an electrician.
我怎么可能不碰电
How the hell am I supposed to do that?
噢 老天
Oh, God.
捍卫者会来找你的 你知道吧
The Champion's coming for you. You know that, right?
正合我意
I'm counting on it.
拜托不要
Please don't.
特斯·亚当 你在哪
Teth Adam. Where are you?
你一直跟着我吗
You followed me?
我的意念和身体可以同时出现在不同地方
My mind and body can exist in different places at the same time.
你找到那个男孩了吗
Did you find the boy?
追上其中一辆摩托车 但那孩子不在里面
Caught one of the bikes, but he didn't have the child.
把抓到的人交给我 我可以读心
Bring me the prisoner. I'll break his mind.
你杀了他对吗
You killed him, didn't you?
他没能撑过去
He didn't make it.
子弹取出来了 组织损伤已经修复
The bullet's extracted. The tissue damage has been repaired.
血压 高压120 低压81 心率每分钟74次
Blood pressure, 120 over 81. Heart rate's at 74 bpm.
他很快就可以重新站起来了
He'll be back on his feet in no time.
太不可思议了
That is insane.
纳米机器人发挥了很大作用
The nanobots did most of the work.
不不不 你太轻描淡写了
No, no, no. I'm not gonna let you downplay this.
我刚才真的是见证了奇迹
I literally just witnessed a miracle.
怎么 我说错话了吗
What? I say something stupid?
没有 我感慨你可以改变自己的分子结构
No, it's just that you can transform your molecular structure,
让身体变大一百倍
grow a hundred times your own size.
你本身就是不可能的存在 看到你令我感到惊奇
You're an impossibility and the world still amazes you.
我也说不清 反正... 挺酷的
I don't know, it's... It's cool.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但还是纳米机器人更酷
But it's not as cool as nanobots.
你就是这样制造风的吗
That's how you do your wind thing.
嗯 准确点叫控风术
Well, the wind thing is called aerokinesis.
这些纳米机器人是被一个疯子科学家注射到我血液里的
And the nanobots were injected into my bloodstream...
我十五岁时被他绑架了
by this really messed-up scientist who kidnapped me when I was 15.
我... 真抱歉
I'm... so sorry.
没关系的
No, you're good.
但是看起来你的确改变了局势
It seems like you really turned it around.
找到了属于你的道路
Found your calling.
真希望我也能这样
Hoping this is mine.
陷入过往是没有意义的
There's no point in dwelling in the past.
过去的事已经翻篇了
It's already moved on from you.
你为什么这么说
Why did you say that?
你之前错信了伊斯梅尔 你在为此责怪自己
You were blaming yourself for trusting Ishmael.
你的心思应该花在能改变的事情上
Your thoughts are beter spent on the things you can change,
而不是那些你不能改变的
not those you can't.
你可以看到未来吗
You see the future?
告诉我怎样救出我儿子
Tell me how I get my son back.
信任我们
By trusting us.
卡里姆就会活下来 我们会救出阿蒙
Karim will live. We will save Amon.
这就是我们要做的
It's what we do.
我猜以前你们都没有门吧
I suppose they didn't have doors in your day.
当然有了 不然我们怎么进屋
Well, of course we did. That's how we entered rooms.
我只是讽刺了一下
What I did there is called sarcasm.
阿蒙在哪 你找到他了吗
Where's Amon? Did you found him?
还没有 但我会找到的 我不会放过抓走他的人
Not yet, but I will. The men who took him will suffer.
或许这些家伙能发挥点作用
Maybe these guys can help.
留着俘虏是有用的 他们可以回答我们的问题
There's an upside to keeping prisoners. They can answer our questions.
你对我儿子做了什么
What did you do with my son?
阿德里亚娜 阿德里亚娜
Adrianna. Adrianna.
我认识到在现代世界不应该伤害俘虏
I've learned that in this modern world, we shouldn't hurt our prisoners.
我们要让他们有尊严 要尊重他们
We should treat them with dignity, respect.
不
No.
让我们从一个简单的问题开始 你们俩会飞吗
Let's start with just one simple question. Can either of you fly?
妈的
Shit.
我想我就在一旁看戏好了
I think I'll sit this one out.
告诉我你们对阿蒙做了什么
Tell me what you did with Amon.
你最好别把这两人扔下去
You'd better not drop those prisoners.
我不是要扔两个·
I'm not going to drop them.
我只扔一个
I'm going to drop one of them.
谁先回答谁活命 他在哪
Whoever ansers first lives. Where is he?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
他在沙漠里 在我们的矿区
He's at our mine in the desert.
我可以带...
I can show...
噢 开玩笑吧
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
你说你不会伤害俘虏的
You said you wouldn't hurt the prisoners.
那是讽刺
That was sarcasm.
不 确切地讲 那是撒谎
No, technically, it was just a lie.
国际帮在沙漠有个矿区
Intergang have a mine in the desert.
-阿蒙在那里  -我知道那里
Amon is there. - I know it.
在哈地迪耶山附近
It's near the Al Hadidiyah Mountains.
我们走
Let's go.
我跟你说过 不许再杀人
I told you, stop killing people.
我看他们活得好好的
They look alive to me.
那是因为我救了他们
Because I saved them.
对 所以我等你来了才动手
Well, that's why I waited until you were there.
我得到了想要的信息 而且没人丧命
I got the information I needed, no one died.
我是按你的要求做的
I did it your way.
他也不是没有道理
He does have a point.
我知道形势紧迫
I know it got lost in all the confusing,
但我们得先解决一些事
but we still have some issues to settle here.
我们知道阿蒙在哪 我们得走了
We know where Amon is. We have to go.
这里可没有什么"我们"
There's no "we" here.
只有英雄和恶人
There are only heroes and there are villains.
你认为自己是个英雄 但你放走这些罪犯
You think yourself a hero, but you would let these criminals go free,
明知道他们会让更多人受苦 除非我们现在了结他们
knowing that many more will suffer at their hands unless we end them now.
英雄从不杀人
Heroes don't kill people.
我杀
Well, I do.
又来了
Here we go.
这是我想的那个东西吗？
Is that what I think it is?
9千克纯净的永恒金属
23 pounds of pure Ethernium,
对比同一时期的文物 密度要大很多
much denser than typical artifacts of the period.
国王的脖子可真硬啊
King must have had a really strong neck.
不 我一动手 他脖子就断了
No, it snapped when I killed him.
那是什么？
What's that?
皇冠的内侧有行字
There's writing on the inside of the rim.
"生乃向死之路"
"Life is the only path to death."
就是这个意思
That's what it says.
生乃向死之路
Life is the only path to death.
显而易见到让人惊讶 会不会有其他含义？
Well, that's surprisingly obvious. Could it have another meaning?
可能意思是...
What if it means, like...
"人生短暂 你必须牢牢把握住心中所爱"
"Life is short. You gotta hold on to what you love."
打住
Stop.
还挺深奥
Deep.
这句话的意思不重要
It doesn't matter what it means.
应该让皇冠永远沉在海底
It should be buried under the ocean for eternity.
等一切结束后 我们也考虑把你丢海里
That's not far from what we had in mind for you when this is over.
或者我把你和皇冠一起埋了
Or I could bury you with it.
我们现在还不能埋皇冠 国际帮要找的就是这个
We can't get rid of it now. It's the one thing that Intergang wants.
相信我 我比任何人都了解这顶皇冠的力量
Believe me, I know more than anyone what this crown is capable of.
但现在必须留着它 直到把我儿子安全救出来
But we have to keep it until my son is safe.
阿德里亚娜... 相信我 我们会救出你儿子的
Adrianna... Trust me, we will get your son back.
这群人不关心你儿子 他们只想打败我
They don't care about him. They just want to defeat me.
把它给我
Hand it over.
我们不能冒险让皇冠落入恶人之手
We can't risk letting this crown fall into the wrong hands.
我们会找到别的方法救你儿子
We will find another way.
不
No.
你喜欢把世界分为善与恶
You like to split the world into good and bad,
当由你划分界限时 这是很容易
but that's easy to do when you're the one drawing the line.
但我只关心阿蒙
All I care about is Amon.
在他获救之前 我们都是一条船上的人
And until he is safe, we're all on the same side.
而你... 你们要齐心协力
And you... you will work together.
把目的地设置为哈地迪耶山
Set a course for the Al Hadidiyah Mountains.
我们黎明时行动
We'll go in at dawn.
我希望你可以好好合作|
I hope you can be a team player.
我喜欢团队合作
I love teams.
你又在讽刺了 是吧
That was sarcasm again, yes?
确实
Very much so.
好吧 只是确认一下
Good. Just checking.
一名智者曾对我说 坏计划总好过没计划
A wise man once told me a bad plan is better than no plan at all.
那也不能制定这么坏的计划啊
That was before we had a very bad plan.
别不爽了
Let it go.
我宁愿和他并肩作战 也不想与他为敌
I'd rather be fighting with him than against him.
他是个杀人犯 肯特
He's a murderer, Kent.
如果他背叛我们 那孩子就死定了
If he turns on us, that kid is as good as dead.
你无法决定他人的生死
You don't get to decide who lives or dies.
那是... 由命运决定的
That's... up to Fate.
你从头盔里看到了什么？
What's the helmet telling you?
有人会死
Somebody's gonna die.
是谁 原子粉碎者？肯定是原子粉碎者
Who is it, Atom Smasher? It's Atom Smasher.
不是他 出人意料
Surprisingly, no.
是我吗？
Is it me?
到时候你会知道的
When it's time for you and I to say goodbye, you'll know.
我只能说...
All I can tell you is...
我们还有时间改变未来
There is still time to change the future.
好好把握机会
Let's use it.
好吧 我猜我们要继续按那个糟糕的计划了
Well, I guess we're sticking with a very bad plan.
国际帮非常重视哈地迪耶矿区
The Al Hadidiyah mine is Intergang's most valued asset.
我们将在这里降落 切断他们的增援
I'm gonna land us right here, cut off their access to reinforcements.
但矿区周围形成了一片天然屏障
But the perimeter of the mine creates a natural fortress.
只有一条路可供出入
There is only one way in, one way out.
他们的飞行摩托巡逻队很容易发现我们
We'll be an easy target for their flybike patrol.
沟通是关键 我们保持同步 否则我们会被包围
Communication is key. We keep in step or we get outflanked.
我们慢慢穿过矿区 仔细搜查 直到找到阿蒙为止
We move through the mine, inch by inch, until we find Amon.
然后就轮到你上场了 你准备好了吗... 该死
This is where you come in. Are you ready... Damn it.
或者我们可以像他那样杀进去
Or we could just do that.
纯净的永恒金属护盾 坚不可摧 即便你也无法打破
Pure Eternium Shield. Unbreakable, even with your powers.
阿蒙
Amon.
你敢动他一下 我就杀光你们
You hurt him, I will kill all of you.
没必要搞出人命 我们只想要皇冠
Nobody has to die. We just want the crown.
不在我们手上
We don't have it.
相信我 皇冠只会带来厄运
Believe me, nothing good will come from that crown.
拿皇冠来 否则免谈
No crown, no negotiation.
皇冠在我这里
I have it.
在这里
It's right here.
放了我儿子 皇冠就是你的
Release my son, you can have it.
你干什么
What do you think you're doing?
国际帮杀了我丈夫 我不会让他们再害死我儿子
Intergang killed my husband. I'm not letting them take my son, too.
他不是你的儿子 这里也不是你的国家
Not your son. Not your country.
这不是你们该做的决定
Not your decision to make.
站住
Stop there.
没关系 你会没事的
It's okay. Nothing is gonna happen to you.
快点交出来
Hand it over, now.
对不起 妈妈
I'm sorry, Mama. - No.
没关系 现在放了阿蒙吧
Now, let Amon go.
我感谢你
I thank you.
我也感谢你的朋友们 把皇冠归还给它的合法所有者
And I thanks your friends for returning this crown to its rightful owner.
和外来侵略者联手 你算什么坎达克的捍卫者？
What kind of Champion of Kahndaq sides with foreign invaders?
你想要的东西已经拿到了
You have what you want.
放了他
Let him go.
伊斯梅尔 你要干什么？
Ishmael, what are you doing?
拿回属于我的东西
Taking back what's mine.
我是伟大的阿克顿王仅存的后裔
I'm the last living descendant of King Ahk-Ton the Great.
有了你们刚刚给我的东西 我将成为下一任
And you have just given me everything I need to become the next...
坎达克之王
king of Kahndaq.
一代又一代 我的家族传承着这段历史
My family passed the knowledge on, you know, one to the next.
我们的祖先打造了这顶皇冠 但却被巫师偷走藏匿起来
This crown, crafted by our ancestors, stolen by the wizards and hidden away.
但只要我们手持这顶皇冠 它便是巨大力量的源泉
But still a source of great power, if only we can wield it.
听说胡劳特死的时候 你哭得像个小孩
They say when Hurut died, you wept like a baby.
你也会为这些人流泪吗？
I wonder if you'll do the same for them.
求求你 伊斯梅尔
Please, Ishmael.
抱歉 阿蒙
Sorry, Amon.
准备好 命运博士
Fate, get ready.
死乃向生之路
Death is the only path to life.
阿蒙
Amon.
他还活着 但我们得送他去医疗舱
He's alive. But we need to get him to the medical bay.
-他哪里中枪了？  -不是枪伤
Where is he shot? - It wasn't a bullet.
是我伤了他
It was me.
走吧
Come.
我们和你一起去
We're going with you.
找到皇冠 把它带回飞船
Just find the crown. Get it on the cruiser.
我找到皇冠了 但还有别的发现
I found the crown. But it's not alone.
我们还要拖延多久
How long we gonna keep doing this?
战斗毫无意义 你我都清楚 没人能阻挡我
There's no point in fighting. We both know no one can stop me.
你说得对
You're right.
只有你自己可以
Only you can.
伊斯梅尔说 胡劳特死去时 你哭了
Ishmael said you cried when Hurut died.
谁是胡劳特
Who's Hurut?
胡劳特是坎达克真正的捍卫者
Hurut was a true Champion of Kahndaq.
他也是 我的儿子
And he was also... my son.
我不可能永远保护你
I won't always be here to protect you.
我不想要保护
I don't need protection.
我想要自由
I want to be free.
自由只属于鸟儿
Freedom is for the birds.
让别人来当英雄吧
Let someone else be the hero...
最终这些英雄都会进坟墓
the graveyards are full of them.
我努力保护他
I tried to protect him.
但我不够强
But I wasn't strong enough.
沙赞
Shazam.
巫师们选中他 让他成为他们的捍卫者
The wizards decided that he would be their champion.
然而在胡劳特所向披靡之时
But after the Champion's many victories,
国王对他最爱的人痛下杀手
the king went after what Hurut loved the most.
那就是我们一家
Our family.
坚持住 父亲
Hold on, Father.
听好我说的话
Stay with me.
有我的力量
With my powers...
你会没事的
you'll be safe.
我没能保护你妈妈
I couldn't protect your mother.
跟着我念
Repeat what I say.
-沙赞  -沙赞
Shazam. - Shazam.
他没有去挑战国王
Instead of battling the king...
也没有去拯救坎达克
Instead of saving Kahndaq...
胡劳特决定救的人
Hurut chose to save...
是我
me.
但他没能逃过国王刺客的暗杀
But he couldn't save himself from the king's assassins.
这份力量并非巫师的祝福
The powers were not a gift from the wizards...
而是一份诅咒
but a curse.
因愤怒而生
Born out of rage.
那座英雄雕像不是你的
The statue of the Champion isn't you.
是胡劳特的
It's Hurut.
我儿子梦想着一个更美好的世界
My son dreamt of a better world.
所以他救了我
That's why he saved me.
但没有他的世界 谈何美好
But the world was only a better place with him in it.
坎达克需要的是一个英雄
Kahndaq needed a hero.
却偏偏选中了我
Instead, it got me.
给我这些力量
All this power...
而我只会用它伤害别人
And the only thing I can do with it is hurt people.
我会说出儿子对我说的话 我会放弃我的能力
I will speak the word my son gave me, and I will give up my power.
但在我说完后 你必须确保我不再念那个咒语
And when I do, you must ensure I never speak it again.
沙赞
Shazam.
有些人注定无法成为
Some men are not meant...
成为英雄
to be heroes.
嘿
Hey.
多美啊
So beautiful.
看到我们惊不惊喜
Surprised to see us?
我们这行可不喜欢惊喜
Surprise is a dirty word in this business.
你确定你能搞定吗
Are you sure you can handle him?
你才是能看到未来的人 如果我们做不到 你肯定会告诉我
You're the one who can see the future, you'll tell me if we can't.
对这位千万要小心点
Just be careful with this one.
他们都说 我们由神明创造
You know, they say the gods created us,
但神明最后却由我们埋葬
but we're the ones who always wind up burying them.
沃勒向你们问好
Waller sends her regards.
他们会知道如何处理他
They'll know how to deal with him.
为了防止他重新获得力量 他们会让他保持假死状态
To keep him from regaining his powers, they'll keep him in suspended animation.
只要让他待在水下 他就无法说话
As long as he's submerged, he won't be able to speak.
什么也说不了
He'll never say another word again.
嘿 他在这呢
Hey. There he is.
不是所有英雄都披披风 但我觉得你应该披一个
Not all heroes wear capes, but I think you earned this.
据统计 大部分英雄都不披披风
Well, statistically, most heroes don't wear capes.
但试试看吧
But yeah, try it on.
看起来还不错
Yeah, looks pretty good.
你配合的也很好
That's a nice touch.
肯特
Kent.
任务完成了吗
Mission accomplished?
我预见的未来没有改变
My vision hasn't changed.
但已经处理好特斯·亚当了
But Teth Adam's out of the equation.
肯特 如果还没有结束 告诉我接下来会怎样
Kent, if this isn't over, I need to know what's coming.
头盔告诉你什么了？
What is the helmet telling you?
我总是看见巨大的灾难发生
My vision has always shown me great calamity.
世界被火焰吞噬
The world in flames.
我们可以阻止它
We can stop it...
但你会死
but you die.
你应该早点告诉我的
You should've told me sooner.
我不怕死
I have no fear of death.
这正是我没有告诉你的原因
That's precisely why I didn't tell you.
世界需要正义协会
The world needs the Justice Society.
世界需要你
The world needs you.
但你不能选择谁生谁死
But you can't choose who lives and dies.
这就是命运吧
That's Fate, right?
嗯 这话听起来耳熟
Well, that sounds familiar.
我记得第一次看到飞机时
I remember seeing my first airplane.
那是一架英国皇家空军的飞机 正前往西部战线
It was an RAF deployment, headed to the Western Front.
我住的街区上所有人都出来为他们送行
Everyone on my street came out to see them off.
但是我没有欢呼
But I didn't cheer.
即使当时我只是个孩子
Even though I was only a boy.
我知道他们要去哪里 等待他们的是什么
I knew where they were headed, and what awaited them.
幸亏有这一点 我才能活这么久
Thanks to this, I've lived longer than I could've ever have hoped for.
我看到世界在以超乎我想象的方式改变
I have seen the world change in more ways than I could've imagined.
我还是一个多愁善感的傻瓜
I'm still a sentimental fool.
我不希望我的朋友去死
And I don't want my friend to die.
伊斯梅尔说"死乃向生之路"
Ishmael said, "Death is the only path to life."
但铭文上不是这么说的
But that's not what the inscription says.
没错 铭文写的是"生乃向死之路"
Right. "Life is the only way to death."
也许他弄反了 就像对着镜子读的那样
Maybe he got it backwards, like he read it in a mirror or something.
没错 在坎达克神话中
That's it. In Kahndaqi mythology,
被诅咒的灵魂会送往终结之石
the souls of the damned are sent to the Rock of Finality.
地狱就像是我们的一面镜子 把它翻转过来
The underworld is a mirror to our own. Here, turn the crown around.
现在把这些字母镜像处理
Now mirror the letters.
看到没 这就是我忽略的地方
See? That's what I missed.
"死乃向生之路"
"Death is the only path to life."
他故意绑架了阿蒙
He kidnapped Amon on purpose,
因为他知道特斯·亚当会杀了他
because he knew that Teth Adam would kill him.
而他相信捍卫者的魔法会送他到终结之石
And he believed the Champion's magic would send him to the Rock of Finality.
就像生命是通向死亡的道路
As life is the path to death.
现在你的死亡也通向生命
Now your death is a path to life.
巫师有他们的捍卫者 现在我们也有自己的
The wizards have their champion, now we have ours.
你将坐上坎达克的王位
You will take the throne of Kahndaq...
将地球变成地狱
and unleash hell on Earth.
说出我们的名字
Speak our name.
"沙巴克"
"Sabbac."
那是什么鬼东西
What the bloody hell is that?
检测器显示是恶魔沙巴克
Readout says it's the demon, Sabbac.
带我过去 快点 快
Get me closer. Now, right now.
距离目标有160公里 给我20秒时间
We're 100 miles out, give me 20 seconds.
你们的国王回来了
The king has returned.
王位是我的
The throne will be mine.
站稳了
Brace yourselves.
抓紧
Hold on.
准备受死吧
Now prepare to die.
等等 卡里姆舅舅去哪了
Wait, wait, where's Uncle Karim?
无论如何 不能让他坐上王位
No matter what happens, he does not sit on that throne.
-收到  -我们正在阻止他
Copy that. - We're on it.
小心
Heads up.
激活红外功能
Activate infrared.
沙巴克 现身吧
Sabbac, show yourself.
阿德里亚娜
Adrianna.
阿蒙
Amon.
这是为了我的飞船
That's for my cruiser.
是时候了
This is it.
卡特 我们赢不了的
We can't win, Carter.
但如果我们输了 世界会毁灭 对吗
Yeah, but the world burns if we don't. Right?
坏计划总好过没计划
Bad plan is better than no plan at all.
不 不 不 你要干什么
No, no, no. What are you doing?
给我们第三个选择
Giving us a third option.
应该是我去才对
It's supposed to be me.
我没把所有事情告诉你 老朋友
I didn't tell you my whole vision, old friend.
我确实预见了你的死亡
I did see your death.
但我也找到了避免它的办法
But I also found a way to prevent it.
我拥有非凡的人生 但总有一直脚踏进未来
It has been an extraordinary life, but always with one foot in the future.
卡特 100年来 这是唯一一次
Carter, for the first time in 100 years,
当我向前看时
when I look ahead...
看不到任何东西
I see nothing.
不 肯特
No, Kent.
并且
And...
这很
it's...
美好
beautiful.
等等 肯特
Wait, Kent.
再见了
Goodbye...
肯特
Kent.
我亲爱的朋友
...my dear friend.
肯特
Kent.
从各个方向击打
Hit it from every side.
肯特
Kent.
不
No.
我是命运博士 巫师 秩序之主代理人
I am Dr. Fate, sorcerer, agent of the Lords of Order,
黑暗和混乱的抵御者
defender against darkness and chaos,
但即便是我的力量 也无法战胜你
but even my powers cannot defeat you.
没人可以战胜我
There's no one that can defeat me.
有一个人可以 有一个人可以
There is one... There is one...
特斯·亚当
Teth Adam.
我知道你能听见我说话
I know you can hear me.
你儿子的战斗落到了我们身上
The battle your son was meant to fight is upon us.
现在只有你能打败恶魔
Now you are the only one who can defeat the Demon Champion.
你拥有毁灭世界的力量
You have the power to be the destroyer of this world.
但你也能拯救世界
But you can also be its savior.
你认为自己不配做英雄 因为巫师没有选择你
You believe you are not a worthy champion because the wizards did not choose you.
但命运不会出错 你的儿子也没错
But Fate does not make mistakes. Neither did your son.
我们看错你了
We were wrong about you.
这个世界并不总是需要白衣骑士
The world doesn't always need a white knight.
有时候它需要更黑暗的东西
Sometimes it needs something darker.
不要放弃我们 这个世界需要你
Don't you dare give up on us now. The world needs you.
肯特
Kent.
不
No.
妈妈
Mom?
怎么回事
What's happening?
是沙巴克
It's Sabbac.
他在指挥地狱军团
He commands the Legions of Hell.
不管发生什么
Whatever happens...
你都要站在我身后
you stay behind me.
别担心 我是被电死的
Don't worry, I die by electricity.
想感受一下坎达克风情吗 来吧
You want some Kahndaq? Come and get it.
来吧
Come and get it.
不不不
No, no. No.
-别又打发我回家 我能帮上忙  -我知道
Don't send me home, I can help. - I know.
但比起抡棍子 你有更重要的事要做
But you can do better than swinging a stick.
众神让我们团聚了
The Gods have brought us together again.
现在还不是时候 父亲
It's not your time, Father.
嘿
Hey.
你们傻站着干什么呢
What are you all standing around for?
我们的机会来了
This is our chance.
我们靠双手建立了坎达克
With these hands, we built Kahndaq.
我们也可以靠双手获得自由
And with these hands, we will set it free.
人民需要一个英雄
The people need a hero.
不 父亲
No, Father.
他们需要自由
They need to be free.
我们还等什么
What are we waiting for?
说出那个词
Say the word.
沙赞
Shazam.
坎达克人民要站起来反抗你
The people of Kahndaq rise up against you.
太棒了
Yes.
交给我吧
I got this.
去打败他
Go get him.
你知道我必须得这么做
You know what I have to do.
爆锤他
Beat his ass.
让真正的勇士一决高下 决定坎达克的命运
Let the fate of Kahndaq be decided by a true battle of champions.
做个了断吧
Let's end this.
他们数量太多了
It's a lot of them.
-比我以为的多了点  -是啊
It's a bit more than I thought. - Yeah.
就多一点点
Just a bit.
嘿 妈妈
Hey, mom.
这是我们的街道 我们的城市
These are our streets. Our city.
解放坎达克
Free Kahndaq.
巫师的力量在你身上都浪费了
The wizards' powers were wasted on you.
你不是英雄
You are not a hero.
是的 我不是英雄
No. I'm not.
但他是
But he is.
你不能违抗我
You cannot stand against me.
我是坎达克真正的捍卫者
I am Kahndaq's true champion.
这是我从一个老朋友那里学到的伎俩
I learned this trick from an old friend.
你可以阻止他
You can control it.
你必须阻止他
You have to.
告诉他们是黑衣人送你来的
Tell them the Man in Black sent you.
-太棒了  -太棒了
Yes. - Yes.
没想到见到你这么开心
I never tought I'd be happy to see you.
我是因为他才来的
I'm only here because of him.
我也一样
That makes two of us.
再见 老朋友
See you around, old friend.
你能让他别惹麻烦吗
Think you can keep him out of trouble?
只要没人来找麻烦就行
As long as no one comes looking for it.
有道理
Fair enough.
只是要小心
Just be careful.
你所奉行的正义会使你的灵魂变得黑暗
The kind of justice you dish out can darken your soul.
正是黑暗 让他有了你这种英雄没有的力量
It's his darkness that lets him do what heroes like you cannot.
走着瞧吧
I guess we'll find out, won't we?
我觉得我们刚才合作得很不错
I tought we made a pretty good team back there.
就是随口一说
Just saying.
我们刚才合作得很不错
We made a great team.
-也许我们可以...  -适可而止
Maybe we could... - Don't push it.
粉碎者 我们走吧
Smasher, let's go.
捍卫者万岁
Long live the Champion.
捍卫者万岁 捍卫者万岁
Long live the Champion. Long live the Champion.
你可以领导他们
You could lead them.
感觉如何
How does it feel?
不对劲
Wrong.
那现在怎么办
So... what now?
意思是你终于要成为我们的英雄了吗
Does this mean you're finally gonna be our hero?
坎达克一直都有英雄
Kahndaq has always had heroes.
现在依旧如此
And it still does.
但现在需要有人保护这座城市
What is needs now is a protector.
谢谢你 特斯·亚当
Thank you, Teth Adam.
这个名字可能有点...
Perhaps that name is a little...
过时了
old-fashioned.
我们应该怎么称呼你？
So what should we call you?
好吧 "黑亚当"
Okay, "Black Adam."
我叫阿曼达·沃勒 恭喜你成功吸引了我的注意
My name is Amanda Waller. Congratulations, you have my attention.
这是我对你唯一的一次警告
This is gonna be your only warning.
你不想待在我的监狱里 没关系
You don't want to stay in my prison, that's fine.
现在坎达克就是你的监狱
Kahndaq is your prison now.
敢迈出一步 你就活不到后悔
You step one foot ouside of it, you will not live to regret it.
这个星球上谁也阻止不了我
There's no one on this planet that can stop me.
我可以求助别人 让他们派其他星球的人来
I can call in a favor and send people who aren't from this planet.
把他们都派来吧
Send them all.
如你所愿
As you wish.
已经很久没有人让这个世界这么紧张了
It's been a while since anyone's made the world this nervous.
黑 亚 当
Black Adam.
我们得谈谈
We should talk.